  return [
        {
          id: 42,
          front: "Senegal",
          back: "Dakar",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 43,
          front: "Seychelles",
          back: "Victoria",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 44,
          front: "Sierra Leone",
          back: "Freetown",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 45,
          front: "Somalia",
          back: "Mogadishu",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 46,
          front: "South Africa",
          back: "Pretoria (administrative) / Cape Town (legislative) / Bloemfontein (judicial)",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 47,
          front: "South Sudan",
          back: "Juba",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 48,
          front: "Sudan",
          back: "Khartoum",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 49,
          front: "Tanzania",
          back: "Dodoma (political) / Dar es Salaam (commercial)",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 50,
          front: "Togo",
          back: "Lom√©",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 51,
          front: "Tunisia",
          back: "Tunis",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 52,
          front: "Uganda",
          back: "Kampala",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 53,
          front: "Zambia",
          back: "Lusaka",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
        {
          id: 54,
          front: "Zimbabwe",
          back: "Harare",
          dueAt: null,
          repetitions: [],
          interval: 1,
        },
      ];